Ukraine can either protect the most important big cities -
- Or the front line, which will be extra important for the counter -offensive.
We have heard that Kiev has good air defense - yet the drones manage to get through.
How to explain it?
An air defense is never 100 percent, but consists of different systems-
- From short-range to medium and very long-range.
The Russian robotic attacks are often a mix.
First it can be exercise robots without explosive charge -
- Or drones, to saturate the air defense systems.
Then you strike with cruise robots with the explosive effect.
An air defense is never 100 percent.
And the drones that cost 200,000-
Russia, then, what does their line of defense look like?
Since October, Russia has actually dug several layers in stock -
–A of minefields, shooting boars and tanks -
- To make the Ukrainian offensive more difficult.
You may not stop it, but you buy time -
- For Russian reinforcements that may come where Ukraine breaks through.
Here it is also important to remember that the Ukrainian counter -offensive -
- Can be several counter -offensives who see where you break through.
If you break through in one direction you can continue there towards different goals.
But most important is to break the supply that goes all the way to Crimea.
- The railway then?
-Yes exactly.